ISAAC "YAK" LITZENBERGER

WEB DEVELOPER & DIGITAL MARKETER

SAN FRANCISCO BAY AREA

i@isaacyakl.com • +1-510-925-3175

isaacyakl.com • github.com/isaacyakl • linkedin.com/in/isaacyakl

Detailed web developer with 5 years of experience designing and developing ecommerce websites and web applications seeking full or part-time front-end position. Demonstrated ability to identify and create result-driven solutions; wrote the #1 most-used Paintball trade-in web app of 2015-2016. Values teamwork, integrity, and user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer & Digital Marketer

New Breed Paintball and Airsoft | 08/2020 - Present

- Programmed industry-leading, trade-in web application
- Automated structured data generation with JavaScript
- Generated average monthly revenue of \$2,000+
- Increased domain authority by 33% through SEO tasks
- Wrote industry specific blogs and reviews
- Created ecommerce SOPs for training and workflow optimization

Key Achievement: Developed website features to save \$100s/mo in third-party application subscriptions

Web Developer & Digital Marketer

YourPbFriend | 03/2014 - 08/2016

- Increased revenue 10x in 2 years by switching to the Shopify platform
- Identified key areas to successfully improve over competitors
- · Created a used gun rating system to successfully build buyer trust
- Embedded YouTube content to educate and create value for customers
- Created ecommerce SOPs for training and workflow optimization

Key Achievement: Developed the #1 most-used paintball trade-in web application of 2015-2016

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Figma

- TypeScript
- HTML
- JSON

- NextJS
- CSS / SASS REST

- ReactJS
- Git / GitHub SEO
- Shopify API PHP

- SEM
- Tailwind CSS Python
- Adobe Apps

PROJECTS

isaacyakl.com - Portfolio

- · Built with NextJS; hosted on Vercel
- Includes web-based resume
- Experiments with relative units instead of breakpoints

Remote Jackbox Player

- · Web app to find and play Jackbox games remotely and for free
- · Uses Twitch API to find people streaming games
- Mobile focused design with multiple viewing formats built with Tailwind CSS and JS

bRando.js

- A CSS background randomizer with support for images, colors, and gradients
- Utilizes image preloading
- Minified and published to NPM and CDN

Keyboard Soundboard

- · A web browser soundboard with preset keybinds and preloaded sound files
- Uses JavaScript to play and stop audio elements
- · Animates buttons when triggered

Random Owen Wowson

- A python Discord bot for sending random Owen Wilson "wow" movie clips
- Makes use of the Owen Wilson Wow API
- Includes a small HTTP status server

COURSES

- React For Beginners wesbos.com
- The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 udemy.com
- Front-End Nanodegree Grow w/ Google
- Computer Science I & II CSUSM

EDUCATION